safe1browsing.net 2016-01-19

# Safe Browsing

In order to protect your privacy and make sure you understand exactly our privacy policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive when you use the Service and/or are Software, Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. has set up this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy may be amended or updated from time to time. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

To fully understand the Service (as defined in Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. Terms) we recommend you to read Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. Terms, available at: http://www.safe1browsing.net/privacy-policy/.

What Personal Information Does Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. Store? Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. retains a unique identifier that is created randomly. This unique identifier is the sole identifiable information retained about you. Apart from this, Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. may retain specific information you provide it or third parties on its behalf.

What Non-Personal Identifying Information Does Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. Store?“Produkt Name“ Ltd. retains some non-personally identifiable information, such as pages you visit, your approximate geolocation, IP address, browser types, time zone, operating system, your default search providers, browser language, operating system language, and other information relating to your use of the Service in order to provide you with better services.

Are Cookies Used? When you use the Service, Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. may store cookies on your computer to identify you for Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. and its partners in providing the Service. These cookies shall be stored until you delete them from your computer. Please note that third party websites which may advertise via the Service and other third party websites that you might interact through your use of the Service may also place or read cookies on your computer’s browser, which enables them to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements and content (e.g. Google Adwords, Google analytics, etc). The collection and use of such information and access of any third party websites are subject to such third party’s privacy policies and so we recommend you to read their privacy policies carefully.

How is the Information Processed? “Produkt Name“ Ltd. processes non-personal information and creates statistical and aggregated information in order to allow better service offer you better deals.

Who has access to the information?Apart from Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. employees and contractors, who are under strict confidentiality and data-protection obligations, no other third party has access to your personal information. Some of Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. affiliates and partners have access to Non-Personal statistical information.

Third Party Advertisements:Some of the Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. websites have 3rd party services implemented inside them for displaying advertisements and for providing with analytical services. Such third party services, such as Google Adwords, may have their own privacy policies

Can I review or remove the Information? As Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. does not retain any Personal Identifying Information, you cannot review or remove any information.

SecurityWe take a great care in maintaining the security of Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. and your information and in preventing unauthorized access to it through industry standard technologies and internal procedures. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.

What to do if you feel your privacy was invaded?If you feel that your privacy was invaded, please contact Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. directly at support@safe1browsing.net and Safe Browsing 1 Ltd. privacy officer shall investigate and post its report promptly.

Our Policy Toward Children: We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 without the consent of the parent or guardian. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@safe1browsing.net  If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.
